{
    "subject": "Raymond_Bernard",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Les_Mis\u00e9rables__1934_film_",
    "human_readable": "Raymond Bernard directed the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9625535607337952,
            "question": "Who directed the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8525142669677734,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Raymond Bernard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842767596244812,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Raymond Bernard."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7425047755241394,
            "question": "What is the source material for the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7332615852355957,
            "question": "What genre is the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934) likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5997651219367981,
            "question": "In what year was Les Mis\u00e9rables (film) made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5958194732666016,
            "question": "What year was the film Les Mis\u00e9rables released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4718080163002014,
            "question": "Is there a film adaptation of the novel Les Mis\u00e9rables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.381824791431427,
            "question": "Are there multiple film adaptations of Les Mis\u00e9rables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27866673469543457,
            "question": "Who are some famous actors who have appeared in adaptations of Les Mis\u00e9rables?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Raymond Bernard directed the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934).",
            "html": "yago_12816_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there multiple film adaptations of Les Mis\u00e9rables?",
            "html": "yago_12816_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a film adaptation of the novel Les Mis\u00e9rables?",
            "html": "yago_12816_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Les Mis\u00e9rables released?",
            "html": "yago_12816_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12816_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12816/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt` explicitly states that the film \"LES MIS\u00c9RABLES\" was directed by Raymond Bernard in 1934, which confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Raymond Bernard directed the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934).\" Both `55.txt` and `23.txt` explicitly mention Raymond Bernard as the director of the film \"Les Mis\u00e9rables\" released in 1934."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}